<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nathan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://kitchvx.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nathan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023 Nathan Kitching</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 22:57:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kitchvx.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Comment Policy</title>
      <link>https://kitchvx.github.io/posts/comment-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 22:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kitchvx.github.io/posts/comment-policy/</guid>
      <description>By commenting on any discussion on this blog you accpet these terms. The Comment Policy is in place under the best interest of the users and the site itself. The policy will detail about what is expected of the users and what is not acceptable, should the policy be broken by any user it will result in a removal of the comment and/or the banning of their account from the blog.</description>
      <content>&lt;h3 id=&#34;accept&#34;&gt;By commenting on any discussion on this blog you accpet these terms.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Comment Policy is in place under the best interest of the users and the site itself. The policy will detail about what is expected of the users and what is not acceptable, should the policy be broken by any user it will result in a removal of the comment and/or the banning of their account from the blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here is what comments should look like:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use a reasonable username or your real name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think before you type - If you disagree with someone that is fine but do not use swear words or any racial slurs, light sarcasm is tolerated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Structure sentances in a coherent manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jokes are tolerated so long as they are not portrayed in a racist or dark manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When in an arguement offer constructive criticism, don&amp;rsquo;t be ignorant or stupid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t post personal information about any user under any circumstances.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;guidelines&#34;&gt;Guidelines&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;All Rights Reserved:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;We reserve the right to edit, delete, move, or mark it as spam. We also reserve the right to block any account that violates this comment policy from commenting.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;Links:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;If you include a link within your comment, the comment won&amp;rsquo;t be approved until the link has been verified and thought to be relevent to the discussion.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;Liability:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;By posting a comment, you agree that your contribution is your own and that you take responsibility for it. You agree to hold Nathan&amp;rsquo;s Blog, Nathan himself and other commenters harmless.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spam:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Spamming comments of any kind in any manner is not allowed and you could be banned from commenting again.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;dt&gt;&lt;em&gt;Privacy:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Do not share private information within your comment. We will delete phone numbers, personal email addresses &lt;em&gt;(Work or buisness emails must be specified)&lt;/em&gt;, or any other private or personal information to protect the affected party, however, your own social media accounts such as twitter will be allowed to be exchanged.&lt;/dd&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for taking time to read this! Remember to be respectful and think before you comment.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kitchvx.github.io/posts/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 18:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kitchvx.github.io/posts/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can reach me at: Email Twitter Telegram Instagram Social Media such as Facebook I am on, however I am inactive. These are the only places you can reach me where I am active, anything else I either no longer use or don&amp;rsquo;t use.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;you-can-reach-me-at&#34;&gt;You can reach me at:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:nathk.nk1214@gmail.com&#34;&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Kitchvx/&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://t.me/Kitchvx/&#34;&gt;Telegram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://instagram.com/kitchh/&#34;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social Media such as Facebook I am on, however I am inactive. These are the only places you can reach me where I am active, anything else I either no longer use or don&amp;rsquo;t use.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kitchvx.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 17:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kitchvx.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me. Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Nathan. I&amp;rsquo;m an 18 y.o tech enthusiast. My hobbies include gaming, video editing, photo manipulation, reading books, socialising with friends and going to the gym. I have a keen interest in computers, computer repair and hardware/software hacking/cybersecurity. I am currently studyin the BTEC Extended Diploma Information Technology at Level 3 in college while persuing apprenticeships for when I leave. In my spare time I like to start projects, such as this Hugo website.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Hi&#34;&gt;Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Nathan.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m an 18 y.o tech enthusiast. My hobbies include gaming, video editing, photo manipulation, reading books, socialising with friends and going to the gym. I have a keen interest in computers, computer repair and hardware/software hacking/cybersecurity. I am currently studyin the BTEC Extended Diploma Information Technology at Level 3 in college while persuing apprenticeships for when I leave. In my spare time I like to start projects, such as this Hugo website. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working two part time jobs, one working at a local bar in my town as a more social experince. While the other job is working for a local shop maintaining and managing the website along with product stocks.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a Site with Hugo.</title>
      <link>https://kitchvx.github.io/projects/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 17:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kitchvx.github.io/projects/website/</guid>
      <description>Overview In this post, I am going to go through the process on how I got to this point in the website project. I will be going over this post in a guide fashion, so it will be treat as such. As I make this the website isn&amp;rsquo;t 100% complete and this will be updated as the site is changed along the way. I created this website as a place to showcase all my projects and proud achievements that will hopefully get the attention of someone that will then use these posts to kickstart their careers or help someone develop a passion.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this post, I am going to go through the process on how I got to this point in the website project. I will be going over this post in a guide fashion, so it will be treat as such. As I make this the website isn&amp;rsquo;t 100% complete and this will be updated as the site is changed along the way. I created this website as a place to showcase all my projects and proud achievements that will hopefully get the attention of someone that will then use these posts to kickstart their careers or help someone develop a passion. Now time to get started!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;prerequisites&#34;&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, the website is built upon the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; framework, before we can get started we need to install Hugo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Installing Hugo:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo is supported on &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MacOS&#34;&gt;macOS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Windows_10&#34;&gt;Windows&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Linux&#34;&gt;Linux&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Berkeley_Software_Distribution&#34;&gt;BSD&lt;/a&gt;. I have been using Windows 10 for the development and deployment at this current stage (22/03/23), I have yet to start using Hugo on &lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/Arch_Linux&#34;&gt;Arch Linux&lt;/a&gt; which is my perfered distribution. The Linux installation is relatively simple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux Installation:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on your distro of choice it will be as simple as typing a few commands for your &lt;a href=&#34;https://itsfoss.com/package-manager/&#34;&gt;package manager&lt;/a&gt;, Hugo&amp;rsquo;s documentation goes over this &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/installation/linux/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me because I use Arch I will use &lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.archlinux.org/title/pacman&#34;&gt;pacman&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update the repositories.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;sudo pacman -Syu
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install Hugo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;sudo pacman -S hugo
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;After Hugo has been installed, make sure you have &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Git&#34;&gt;git&lt;/a&gt; as we will be using this too but this should already be installed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install git.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;sudo pacman -S git
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows Installation:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Windows installation isn&amp;rsquo;t as simple as Linux&amp;rsquo;s installation, who could&amp;rsquo;ve guessed? Firstly you will need to acquire the .zip file and make sure &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Git&#34;&gt;git&lt;/a&gt; is installed, the download for git can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://git-scm.com/download/win&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. If you have no way of unzipping the .zip file you can head to &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WinRAR&#34;&gt;winrar&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.win-rar.com/start.html?&amp;amp;L=0&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; to install it, free of charge. Now we can head to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gohugoio/hugo/releases&#34;&gt;Hugo release&lt;/a&gt; page on github to install the latest version (at the time of writting it the latest version is v0.111.3). Once these have been acquired we can start. Extract the files from the zip file, I have placed my Hugo install into &lt;code&gt;C:\Hugo\bin&lt;/code&gt;, and you will then want to open up the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/search?q=what+is+windows+environment+variables&#34;&gt;Environment Variables&lt;/a&gt; Editor(?) you can find this by pressing &lt;code&gt;Win + R&lt;/code&gt; and typing &lt;code&gt;SystemPropertiesAdvanced&lt;/code&gt; in to the dialogue box you then want to find &lt;code&gt;Path&lt;/code&gt; under User variables for your user, press edit&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://kitchvx.github.io/images/envtable1.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Screenshot 1&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  style=&#34;border-radius: 8px;&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;and add your Hugo binaries to it (this will be the location you have the &lt;code&gt;Hugo.exe&lt;/code&gt; in).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://kitchvx.github.io/images/envtable2.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Screenshot 2&#34;  class=&#34;center&#34;  style=&#34;border-radius: 8px;&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Once this is done we can start using Hugo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My current setup for this is using the terminal to setup a new Hugo site and commit any changes made to Github while using &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Visual_Studio_Code&#34;&gt;Visual Studio Code&lt;/a&gt; to edit text/code. Alternatively you can use VS Code to commit changes to Github by installing the &lt;a href=&#34;https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=GitHub.vscode-pull-request-github&#34;&gt;Github Pull&lt;/a&gt; extenstion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;using-hugo&#34;&gt;Using Hugo&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First things first, you will want to create a github repo and name it something relevent like, for example, &amp;ldquo;kitch-blog&amp;rdquo;. Mine is just called &amp;ldquo;hugo&amp;rdquo;, add a license if you feel the need to. Then we need to create the submodule repository, you will want to name this your username followed by &amp;ldquo;github.io&amp;rdquo;, mine for example is &amp;ldquo;kitchvx.github.io&amp;rdquo;. Now getting the theme is as simple as going to &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io&#34;&gt;themes.gohugo.io&lt;/a&gt;. The theme I used is called &lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/themes/hugo-theme-terminal/&#34;&gt;terminal&lt;/a&gt;. before we clone the theme or start using hugo we need to clone the first repository and to do this you use the following command in your terminal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;git clone https://github.com/YOUR_NAME/YOUR_REPO.git
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cd inside the repository using &lt;code&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; command and use the &lt;code&gt;hugo new site&lt;/code&gt; command to generate a static website, you have to name it, I went with &lt;code&gt;hugo new site kitchblog&lt;/code&gt; and it will generate a site inside a new folder within the repository, cd into it and clone the theme:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;git clone https://github.com/panr/hugo-theme-terminal.git themes/terminal
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before creating the submodule we need to setup the config and make sure everything is working, for the terminal theme the config should be on the&lt;a href=&#34;https://themes.gohugo.io/themes/hugo-theme-terminal/&#34;&gt;hugo themes&lt;/a&gt; page but if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to take the small detour, I will embed the code.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34; checked /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;1&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;toml&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Terminal Theme Configs&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-toml&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
baseurl = &amp;#34;/&amp;#34; # Set this to your website url.
languageCode = &amp;#34;en-us&amp;#34;
theme = &amp;#34;terminal&amp;#34;
paginate = 5

[params]
  # dir name of your main content (default is `content/posts`).
  # the list of set content will show up on your index page (baseurl).
  contentTypeName = &amp;#34;posts&amp;#34;

  # [&amp;#34;orange&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;blue&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;red&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;green&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;pink&amp;#34;]
  themeColor = &amp;#34;orange&amp;#34;

  # if you set this to 0, only submenu trigger will be visible
  showMenuItems = 2

  # show selector to switch language
  showLanguageSelector = false

  # set theme to full screen width
  fullWidthTheme = false

  # center theme with default width
  centerTheme = false

  # if your resource directory contains an image called `cover.(jpg|png|webp)`,
  # then the file will be used as a cover automatically.
  # With this option you don&amp;#39;t have to put the `cover` param in a front-matter.
  autoCover = true

  # set post to show the last updated
  # If you use git, you can set `enableGitInfo` to `true` and then post will automatically get the last updated
  showLastUpdated = false

  # set a custom favicon (default is a `themeColor` square)
  # favicon = &amp;#34;favicon.ico&amp;#34;

  # Provide a string as a prefix for the last update date. By default, it looks like this: 2020-xx-xx [Updated: 2020-xx-xx] :: Author
  # updatedDatePrefix = &amp;#34;Updated&amp;#34;

  # set all headings to their default size (depending on browser settings)
  # oneHeadingSize = true # default

  # whether to show a page&amp;#39;s estimated reading time
  # readingTime = false # default

  # whether to show a table of contents
  # can be overridden in a page&amp;#39;s front-matter
  # Toc = false # default

  # set title for the table of contents
  # can be overridden in a page&amp;#39;s front-matter
  # TocTitle = &amp;#34;Table of Contents&amp;#34; # default


[params.twitter]
  # set Twitter handles for Twitter cards
  # see https://developer.twitter.com/en/docs/tweets/optimize-with-cards/guides/getting-started#card-and-content-attribution
  # do not include @
  creator = &amp;#34;&amp;#34;
  site = &amp;#34;&amp;#34;

[languages]
  [languages.en]
    languageName = &amp;#34;English&amp;#34;
    title = &amp;#34;Terminal&amp;#34;
    subtitle = &amp;#34;A simple, retro theme for Hugo&amp;#34;
    owner = &amp;#34;&amp;#34;
    keywords = &amp;#34;&amp;#34;
    copyright = &amp;#34;&amp;#34;
    menuMore = &amp;#34;Show more&amp;#34;
    readMore = &amp;#34;Read more&amp;#34;
    readOtherPosts = &amp;#34;Read other posts&amp;#34;
    newerPosts = &amp;#34;Newer posts&amp;#34;
    olderPosts = &amp;#34;Older posts&amp;#34;
    missingContentMessage = &amp;#34;Page not found...&amp;#34;
    missingBackButtonLabel = &amp;#34;Back to home page&amp;#34;

    [languages.en.params.logo]
      logoText = &amp;#34;Terminal&amp;#34; # Enter your blog name here, mine is &amp;#34;Nathan&amp;#39;s Blog&amp;#34;.
      logoHomeLink = &amp;#34;/&amp;#34;

    [languages.en.menu]
      [[languages.en.menu.main]]
        identifier = &amp;#34;about&amp;#34;
        name = &amp;#34;About&amp;#34;
        url = &amp;#34;/about&amp;#34;
      [[languages.en.menu.main]]
        identifier = &amp;#34;showcase&amp;#34;
        name = &amp;#34;Showcase&amp;#34;
        url = &amp;#34;/showcase&amp;#34;

[module]
  # In case you would like to make changes to the theme and keep it locally in you repository,
  # uncomment the line below (and correct the local path if necessary).
  # --
  # replacements = &amp;#34;github.com/panr/hugo-theme-terminal -&amp;gt; themes/terminal&amp;#34;
[[module.imports]]
  path = &amp;#39;github.com/panr/hugo-theme-terminal&amp;#39;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;If you are unsure what to do, you can mess around with the configs and check out what everything does. Before seeing the changes you will need to open a terminal and run:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo serve -t terminal
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or you can run it with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-html&#34; data-lang=&#34;html&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo serve --disableFastRender --ignoreCache -t terminal
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flag &lt;code&gt;--disbaleFastRender&lt;/code&gt;  enables full re-renders on changes and the flag &lt;code&gt;--ignoreCache&lt;/code&gt; ignores the cache directory for faster rebuilding times on local previews when saving changes. Now these times aren&amp;rsquo;t significant but when developing on lower end machines it may help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without &lt;code&gt;--disableFastRender&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;--ignoreCache&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://kitchvx.github.io/images/example1-render-times.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Example 1&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  style=&#34;border-radius: 8px;&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;p&gt;With &lt;code&gt;--disableFastRender&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;--ignoreCache&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://kitchvx.github.io/images/example2-render-times.png&#34;  alt=&#34;Example 2&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  style=&#34;border-radius: 8px;&#34;  /&gt;


&lt;h1 id=&#34;comments&#34;&gt;Comments&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
