<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Nathan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://kitch.blog/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Nathan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023 Nathan Kitching</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 22:59:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kitch.blog/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Job</title>
      <link>https://kitch.blog/posts/first-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 22:59:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kitch.blog/posts/first-job/</guid>
      <description>About the Job Just over a couple weeks ago I started my first job within the IT Industry. It&amp;rsquo;s giving me great work experince in using the different WordPress tools such as Elementor, Slider Revolution and WooCommerce I&amp;rsquo;m currently designing and developing a website for a local shop in my town, once the site has gone through the design, staging, optimisation and testing phases I will link it. Designing the product pages, catagories, using photoshop and utilising slider revolution to display the deals that are currently on I am working on adding the different products that the business sells along with optimising SEO.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-the-job&#34;&gt;About the Job&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just over a couple weeks ago I started my first job within the IT Industry. It&amp;rsquo;s giving me great work experince in using the different &lt;a href=&#34;https://wordpress.com/&#34;&gt;WordPress&lt;/a&gt; tools such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://elementor.com/&#34;&gt;Elementor&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sliderrevolution.com/&#34;&gt;Slider Revolution&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://woocommerce.com/&#34;&gt;WooCommerce&lt;/a&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m currently designing and developing a website for a local shop in my town, once the site has gone through the design, staging, optimisation and testing phases I will link it. Designing the product pages, catagories, using photoshop and utilising slider revolution to display the deals that are currently on I am working on adding the different products that the business sells along with optimising &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Search_engine_optimization&#34;&gt;SEO&lt;/a&gt;. When the website has passed the testing period it will go live and I will be tasked with maintaining the website to make sure everything goes smoothly, I will be writting documentation on the webiste for people in the future who are hired to maintain the website as the last person to create a website for the shop didn&amp;rsquo;t provide any information or documentation maaking troubleshooting harder than it needed to be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Web design and development is fun and helps me show my skills however I don&amp;rsquo;t see myself having a career in it but I do see myself potentially doing freelance for small business and individuals that need a website, like my friend who I am currently creating a website for, using hugo. I will also be managing this website for him as he doesn&amp;rsquo;t know how to use the command line or have any tools to do back-end development for a webiste using the hugo framework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading my small post about my job, didn&amp;rsquo;t have much to say just decided to write about it a little. you can check out my projects &lt;a href=&#34;https://kitch.blog/projects/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;comments&#34;&gt;Comments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://kitch.blog/posts/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 18:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kitch.blog/posts/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can reach me at: Email Twitter Telegram Instagram Social Media such as Facebook I am on, however I am inactive. These are the only places you can reach me where I am active, anything else I either no longer use or don&amp;rsquo;t have.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;you-can-reach-me-at&#34;&gt;You can reach me at:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:nathan@kitch.blog&#34;&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Kitchvx/&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://t.me/Kitchvx/&#34;&gt;Telegram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://instagram.com/kitchh/&#34;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social Media such as Facebook I am on, however I am inactive. These are the only places you can reach me where I am active, anything else I either no longer use or don&amp;rsquo;t have.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://kitch.blog/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 17:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kitch.blog/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me. Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Nathan. I&amp;rsquo;m an 18 y.o tech enthusiast. My hobbies include gaming, video editing, photo manipulation, reading books, socialising with friends and going to the gym. I have a keen interest in computers, computer repair and hardware/software hacking/cybersecurity. I am currently studyin the BTEC Extended Diploma Information Technology at Level 3 in college while persuing apprenticeships for when I leave. In my spare time I like to start projects, such as this Hugo website.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Hi&#34;&gt;Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Nathan.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m an 18 y.o tech enthusiast. My hobbies include gaming, video editing, photo manipulation, reading books, socialising with friends and going to the gym. I have a keen interest in computers, computer repair and hardware/software hacking/cybersecurity. I am currently studyin the BTEC Extended Diploma Information Technology at Level 3 in college while persuing apprenticeships for when I leave. In my spare time I like to start projects, such as this Hugo website. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working two part time jobs, one working at a local bar in my town as a more social experince. While the other job is working for a local shop maintaining and managing the website along with product stocks.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
